<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Raskell</title><link>https://raskell.io/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Raskell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://raskell.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>All beginning is Haskell</title><link>https://raskell.io/articles/all-beginning-is-haskell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raskell.io/articles/all-beginning-is-haskell/</guid><description>The beauty of mathematics Mathematics is often considered beautiful because it provides a way to describe and understand the world in a way that is precise, elegant, and abstract. Mathematics can be seen as a language that allows us to describe complex phenomena and patterns in a way that is independent of the particular objects or situations involved. This abstract quality of mathematics is what makes it so powerful and beautiful.</description></item><item><title>My OpenBSD journey: Getting it virtualized with libvirt (1)</title><link>https://raskell.io/articles/my-openbsd-journey-getting-it-virtualized-with-libvirt-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raskell.io/articles/my-openbsd-journey-getting-it-virtualized-with-libvirt-1/</guid><description>Void Linux as my daily driver Around six months ago, I decided to ditch my long in the tooth Arch-based setup on my belovest Thinkpad X1 Carbon. I&amp;rsquo;ve been very loyal over the years, and almost came to belive that Arch will be a constant in my adult life. While I kept up with upcoming technologies, I somehow lost track of the ever so diversifying landscape of Linux distributions.</description></item><item><title>Hello and outlook</title><link>https://raskell.io/articles/hello-and-outlook/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raskell.io/articles/hello-and-outlook/</guid><description>Hello world Welcome to my tech blog! My name is Raffael and I am excited to share my rumings about the state of tech, open-source, and the life as a software developer with you.
In this first post, I wanted to introduce myself and explain what you can expect to find on this blog. I have been working in the tech industry for several years, and I have experience with a variety of technologies, programming languages, and operating systems.</description></item></channel></rss>